playcanvas.com 2012-10-16

# PlayCanvas | Privacy Policy

**PlayCanvas Ltd privacy policy**  
This privacy policy sets out how PlayCanvas Ltd uses and protects any information that you give PlayCanvas Ltd when you use this website.

PlayCanvas Ltd is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

PlayCanvas Ltd may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from [date].

**What we collect**  
We may collect the following information:

  * name and job title
  * contact information including email address
  * Information you provide by filling in forms on our websites. This includes information provided when registering, posting content or subscribing to services.
  * Information that you provide by interacting with tools that submit content or information to our websites or services.
  * Survey responses, for research purposes
  * Details of your visits to our website including, but not limited to, traffic data, location data, weblogs and other communication data.

**What we do with the information we gather**  
We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

  * Internal record keeping.
  * We may use the information to improve our products and services.
  * We may periodically send emails about new products, services or information that you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
  * To inform you about changes to our service.
  * To complete orders or carry out obligations from any contracts entered into between you and us.

**Security**  
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

**How we use cookies**  
A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about webpage traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

**Links to other websites**  
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

**Controlling your personal information**  
We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties.

You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to 191 PLOUGH WAY, LONDON, SE16 7FN, UNITED KINGDOM.

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
